stacymakescents.com 2016-11-15

# Privacy Policy - Humorous Homemaking

### Summary

You’re here because you chose to be here.  I didn’t pay you to show up and I’m not sharing your detailed personal information with BIG BROTHER…or anyone else for that matter.  While you’re here you can expect to be relatively safe, unless you read something I wrote that offends you.  If that happens…oh well.  It is MY blog and everyone in the world isn’t going to agree with me.  However, because the government requires me to disclose lots of silly things because some not-so-nice people tried to do some devious things with your information, I have to tell you about how your privacy matters to me and how it is affected by you visiting Humorous Homemaking.  So…since no one ever posts any of their personal information on Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, Tumblr, SMS, Vine, MySpace, LinkedIn, YouTube or any of those other places we like to hang out, here’s to keeping your privacy…well…private.  And heck, I even made it sound nice and formal.

### Privacy

We care about your privacy.  This notice outlines our online information practices so you can make an informed decision about our practices and whether or not to continue visiting Humorous Homemaking.  This notification is linked from the main menu of our homepage and every page where personally identifiable information is requested.

### Advertisers and Tracking

Humorous Homemaking utilizes third party ad servers or ad networks which may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In doing so, these vendors may collect _**non-personal**_ data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours.  The usage of these cookies is outlined on each advertiser’s own privacy policy. Additionally, generic, non user-specific data is tracked using Google Analytics and similar software to measure visitor statistics as a whole.  Individual, personally-identifiable data is not captured directly by Humorous Homemaking for any purpose, unless you voluntarily provide it to enter a contest or sign up for our communications.

### RSS & Email

Visitors can subscribe to Humorous Homemaking through RSS or email subscription.  If you voluntarily provide your email address for these services, it will be held in strict confidence.  We do not sell or disclose specific subscriber information for any reason, unless required by law.  Summary data void of personally-identifiable information may be disclosed.

### Comments

Comments submitted at Humorous Homemaking are the responsibility of the commenter.  As outlined on our comment policy, provided on every page and post that accepts comments, we reserve the right to remove or edit comments at our sole discretion.  Humorous Homemaking reserves the right to delete any comments it deems inappropriate for any reason. Additionally, once published, comments on Humorous Homemaking become the property of Humorous Homemaking and may be used at our discretion for “testimonials” (or more) elsewhere.

### Links to Third Parties

Humorous Homemaking has links to numerous third party websites.  We cannot control the responsible use of those sites.  When you leave the domain of Humorous Homemaking, this privacy policy no longer applies.

### Changes/Updates and Opt Out

This privacy policy was last updated on February 6, 2015.  The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, for any reason.  [Contact us](http://www.humoroushomemaking.com/contact) if you have questions about any of the ways your privacy may be impacted by visiting Humorous Homemaking or if you believe any information we’re holding is incorrect or incomplete, or you wish to opt out of any/all tracking mechanisms. You can also opt out of cookies using the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page at this page: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>. Finally, you can choose to disable or selectively turn off cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings.
